https://www.enibas.com/privacy-policy/

By continuing to use this website, you consent to the use of cookies in accordance with our
Cookie Policy
You must enable Javascript in your browser to use this website.
Sign InMy Wishlist
Basket (0)
Your shopping basket is currently empty.
0
Shipping Info30 Day promise1 Year Guarantee
Privacy Policy
JewellerySeodraPendants & NecklacesRingsBraceletsStacking RingsEarringsCufflinksPersonalised JewelleryAll JewelleryANAM
Jewellery
Discover ...
Enibas collectionBailiúchán énibasCroí álainnFollow Your DreamLas mo shlí ~ Light my wayMy dreamYour LifeSonasCoinAnna LeahANAM
Enibas Collections
Explore ...
ANAMANAMEnibas GoldÓR ENIBASPendantsRingsBraceletsEarringsAll gold jewelleryGiftsBronntanaisSchull BaubleGift CardsGifts under €80Children's GiftsGifts under €150Wedding GiftsAnniversary GiftsBirthday Gifts
Gifts
Browse ...
Guest designersAoi aoídhearthóiríVolker LangAlan ArdiffDalaleoMaureen LynchLa MollaLinda UhlemannInstagram Shop
Guest designers
Explore ...
Your Storiesdo scéalta
HomeAccountPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
ENIBAS is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets out how we, as a Data Controller, collect, use, process and disclose the personal data  (“Data”) that we collect from you, or that you provide to us, on our website www.enibas.com (“Site”). This Privacy Statement should be read in conjunction with our Cookie Policy.
Please read the following carefully to understand our use of your Data.
1. Information we may collect from you
We only collect Data about you on the Site which you volunteer when you order online on our Site, email us or by using our online Contact Us or other forms (including participation in our surveys); or if you report a problem with our Site. When you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. We also collect Data automatically when you navigate through our Site, as explained in our Cookie Policy.
We may collect and process the following data about you:
your name;
your phone number;
your email address;
your address;
information that you provide by filling in forms on our Site;
the time and date of your visit;
your IP address;
your browser type; and
your referring URL
Unless you place a product order with us, the provision of your Data is not a statutory or contractual requirement and you may refuse to disclose same.
2. Uses made of your data
We may use your Data where necessary for our legitimate business interests, including to:
improve the content of our Site and the products we offer;
ensure the Site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;
compile statistical data on the use of our Site;
allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so; and
notify you about changes to our products.
We make no attempt to identify individual visitors, or to associate the technical details we collect with any individual, unless required to disclose such information by law. We may use your Data to comply with any legal obligations.
We will store your personal Data only for as long as necessary for the purposes of providing access to our Site and related services to you; as required by law, and for the exercise or defence of any legal claims.
3. Disclosure of your information
We will not disclose your Data to third parties unless you have consented to this disclosure or unless the third party is required to fulfil a request you have made or contract that you have entered into.  Where appropriate, Data may also be processed by our service providers in which case we will take steps to ensure that the processing complies with applicable data protection and confidentiality laws. We will also disclose your Data if we believe in good faith that we are required to disclose it in order to comply with any applicable law, a summons, a search warrant, a court or regulatory order or other statutory or legal requirement.
We may provide Non-Personal Data to third parties, where such information is combined with similar information of other users of our Site.  For example, we might inform third parties regarding the number of unique users who visit our Site, the demographic breakdown of our community users of our Site or the activities that visitors to our Site engage in while on our Site.  The third parties to whom we may provide this information may include web developers, server providers, providers of advertising services (including website tracking services), commercial partners, sponsors, licensees, researchers and other similar parties.
4. Links to other sites
Our Site may, from time to time, contain links to and from other websites. If you follow a link to any of those websites, please note that those websites have their own privacy policies and we do not accept any responsibility or liability for those policies. Please check those policies before you submit any Data to those websites.
5. Your rights
You may request access to, rectification, erasure or restriction of your Data, or object to the processing of your Data or Data portability at any time. We will respond to your request in writing, or orally if requested, as soon as practicable and in any event within one month of receipt of your request. We may request proof of identification to verify your request. All requests should be addressed to info@enibas.com .
You have the right to lodge a complaint with the Data Protection Commissioner if you are unhappy with how we are processing your Data.
6. Security and where we store your personal data
We are committed to protecting the security of your Data. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your Data from unauthorised access and use. As effective as modern security practices are, no physical or electronic security system is entirely secure. We cannot guarantee the complete security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. We have implemented strict internal guidelines to ensure that your privacy is safeguarded at every level of our organisation.  We will continue to update policies and implement additional security features as new technologies become available. Where we have given you a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping that password confidential.  We ask you not to share your password with anyone.
Although we will do our best to protect your Data, we cannot guarantee the security of your Data transmitted to our Site. Any transmission of Data is at your own risk. Once we receive your Data, we will use appropriate security measures to seek to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure.
7. Changes to this Privacy Statement
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Statement from time to time at our sole discretion. If we make any changes, we will post those changes here and update the “Last Updated” date at the bottom of this Privacy Statement. Your continued use of this Site after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check this Statement periodically for updates.
8. Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns regarding how your Data is processed via this Site, please contact us at info@enibas.com or write to us at ENIBAS, Main Street, Schull, Co Cork. All requests will be dealt with promptly and efficiently.
Last updated June 2018
Explore Enibas
Our Story
Our BoutiquesWest Cork Design StudioOur StockistsEngravingCareersWhat customers say
Services
FAQContact UsShipping & DeliveryReturns Our GuaranteeRing SizingGift WrappingJewellery CareOpening Hours
Account
Cookie PolicyPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsView your Wish ListAccount LoginSign Up for An AccountUnsubscribe
